<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>analytics on Colin Paulish</title>
    <link>https://colinpaulish.com/tags/analytics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in analytics on Colin Paulish</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 02:01:58 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://colinpaulish.com/tags/analytics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Loss &amp; Damage Fund</title>
      <link>https://colinpaulish.com/blog/loss_and_damage/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://colinpaulish.com/blog/loss_and_damage/</guid>
      <description>Overview General consensus coming out of COP27 was disappointment. Commitments once again exceeded action and many climate enthusiasts left with more questions than answers. An exciting development that did come out of COP27 was the agreement of a ‘Loss and Damage’ fund. In principle, this agreement formalizes mostly rich countries&#39; acknowledgement that there is a need for financial assistance to developing nations facing the brunt of the effects of climate change.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Energy Transition and Jobs</title>
      <link>https://colinpaulish.com/blog/jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://colinpaulish.com/blog/jobs/</guid>
      <description>Opening It’s hard to fault policymakers and local leaders in fossil-fuel heavy regions for their pushback towards green legislation. Shifts in status quo are scary, particularly when the writing on the wall is in sharpie - renewable jobs are coming, and they will negatively impact fossil fuel employment. Industrial shifts can and have brought huge pain to governments, local economies, families, and people. From 1950 to 2000, the “Rust Belt’s” share of US manufacturing employment fell from one-half to one-third with similar magnitude drops when taking a step back calculating aggregate-level employment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
